Hi guys, welcome to the IELTS Reading course.
I'm Francois, your instructor in this course.
Before learning the knowledge and skills to handle
challenging IELTS reading questions, we're going to get
to know a little bit about our IELTS
reading tests and have an overview of the course.
I'm very excited to share valuable knowledge with
you and I hope you're also excited to
learn high quality lessons prepared by the academic team at PREP.
So are you ready?
Let's get started.
First, let's take a look at the test time for IELTS reading.
For paper-based tests, you have 60 minutes
to read, answer questions and transfer your answers
to the answer sheet.
Please note that in IELTS reading tests,
we don't have 10 minutes to transfer answers to
the answer sheet like in the listening tests.
Therefore, you need to read and transfer your
answers at the same time.